From the documentation, we want singleChoice, mode so
that the list item only shows one selected item at a time.
You can declare this attribute on the list view in the fragment_main file.
However, we don't want to specify ChoiceMode in one ping mode. So, to
have these different code paths, we could copy the file in the Layout folder and
put it in the Layout and put it in the Layout-sw600dp folder.
A better solution is to declare a style. So, we have one layout file but
different styles. In the Base styles file in the values folder,
we declare ForecastListStyle. We leave it empty because we don't need to
specify ChoiceMode. We create a new styles file in the values-sw600dp folder.
In the two pane case, the ForecastListStyle does include the ChoiceMode.
The two files have a different number of styles. If it's not declared in
a higher folder, then it will just fall back to the Base style.